# VISMAY THAKER UNITY | AR/VR DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

✓ vismaythaker008@gmail.com

**4** 9427258180

**♦** Ahmedabad,India

**SUMMARY** 

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/thakervismay/

♠ TheDayDreamer 17

Self-taught Unity Developer and a passionate gamer. I have worked on some great games of different genres. AR/VR has always brought some sparkles to my eyes. Vuforia, AR core, Wikitude are my top tools. I have worked with Microsoft Holo lens, Oculus devices, and the MRtoolkit, VRTK.

# **EMPLOYMENT**

# Yudiz Solutions Private Limited Ahmedabad,India

Unity Developer · Dec. 2019 to Current

Worked collaboratively with highly skilled Unity Developers.

- Created a few Clone games and personal prototypes Like Doodle
  Jump clone named Ninja Jump, BasketBall 3d, 2d Procedural mesh
  generation from users Touch input points, Sequence Game (Card
  Game).
- Worked on some good Client Projects in different genres like ML, Match 2, Endless runner along VR Simulations.
- Worked on multiple games simultaneously and communicated with Clients to ensure that the company's goals and requirements were met.
- Learned Unity Unit Testing and prepared a demo (Refer to the Projects Section).
- Proactively indulged in all Team bonding activities and Organized some krunker tournaments (well I almost won all XD)
- Guided the trainees in their training period by taking sessions regarding crucial concepts of Unity.
- Worked on R&D Projects such as Implementing the Marching cubes algorithm, Mesh Deformation, Raymarching, Job System.
- Optimized some of our projects using Profiler, Occlusion culling, Reducing Batch calls, Using ECS
- Looked into the new and emerging coding Paradigm called DOTS and worked on a project using ECS and DOTS.

### AriseGroup Remote Work

Augmented Reality Developer (Contract) -

June 2019 to Dec. 2019

- · Created an AR app using Unity and ARCore
- Gave creative feedbacks on features enhancement and UI design
- Created custom UI scroll tool (Refer the Projects Section for more details)

## Royal Technosoft Ahmedabad, India

Part Time Faculty · June 2018 to Dec. 2018

- Taught students from 10th standard to students pursuing Graduation in C, C++, JAVA, and Unity Development.
- Enlighted them with High-level C, C++ Tests to improve their thinking.
- Created Game in Unity simultaneously with teaching the core physics and collision concepts.

### Royal Technosoft Ahmedabad. India

HoloLens Trainee

- Started a Group to learn and guide others on developing apps on Microsoft Hololens using Unity Game Engine
- Created a few Simple Prototypes in Holo Lens

# **SKILLS**

**KEY SKILLS:** Unity, Blender, Good verbal communication skills, Documentation writing

**PLUGINS:** AR Core, Unity IAP, Log Viewer, DoTween, Google Ads, Facebook sdk, Photon, Remote Config, Cinemachine, Vuforia, Wikitude

**UNITY COMPONENTS:** ML Agents, Unit Testing, AssetBundles, JSON and APIs, Scriptable Objects, Light Baking, Physics, Particle System, Animation Controllers, Timeline, Blend Tree, Editor Scripting

SHADERS: ShaderGraph, HLSL Shaders

LANGUAGES: C, C#, C++, Java Script, Python, PHP, JAVA

# **RECOGNITION**

#### DA-IICTCo-Ordinator for an AR/VR Workshop

- Co-ordinated the workshop for AR/VR development in Hololens using Unity Game Engine.
- Presented and explained my creation of ID Badge used by our whole team created using Vuforia tool.

#### Digimation PVT LTD · Job Requirement Counselor

- I had represented the company Digimation PVT LTD as a Requirement Counsellor at Marwadi University
- Explained the last year students about various IT field jobs and then guide them for their suitable job

# **CREATIVITY**

Drama · Lead Role in commercial play named "TAX FREE"

Content Creator on Youtube · Youtuber

I am a free time content creator, creating funny videos about the famous topics and producing some funny Valorant gameplay clips

# **EDUCATION**

Gujarat Technological University · Aug. 2016 to Aug. 2020 B.E. Computer Engineering 2020 CGPA-8.99

Shree Narayana Guru Vidyalaya -June 2014 to June 2016 HSC Percentage - 70.6%

Shree Narayana Guru Vidyalaya -June 2013 to June 2014 SSC Percentage - 77.6%



# **PROJECTS**

#### AriseGroup

- This is an AR App showing the details and an AR view of all the buildings created by Arise Group of Builders created using Unity engine and AR Core.
- · As the models of Buildings used by builders are very detailed. had to reduce the polygon count for getting stable fps.
- I have used Assetbundles to store the data and 3d models.
- Added an EMI Calculator within the app along with ChatBot and chat on WhatsApp.
- · Created my Custom horizontal Scroll view to give a materialistic android view of Scrollable Fading Cards.

#### Vuforia ID Cards

- I created unique Scannable Id cards using Vuforia's vumark technology.
- · We embossed the remarks on the physical badges and created each with unique data of that person
- We represented this in the workshop at AR/VR at DA-IICT.
- The Id Badges when scanned from our app show details of that person like name and designation.

#### Bowman

It is a single-player game in which the user has to shoot enemies and climb the ladder until he kills the boss and moves to another level.

- · Implemented Spine in Unity.
- Created endless Levels mechanism.
- Added unique Unlockable skins and weapons for Protagonist.
- · Created Spin Wheel and added Unity IAP.

#### **Toony Bricks**

Toony Bricks is a family of match-based games where the User matches 2 or more matching tiles to clear the level.

- Created a custom level generator
- Designed 100 attractive and gradually challenging levels.
- Added Daily Bonus.
- Developed Gift Boxes, Collectibles, Boosters, and Powerups.
- Created a custom algorithm that can generate level boundaries using Line renderer.

#### **Toon Brick Unit Testing**

- As a personal project, I applied almost all Unity Unit testing fetures in my ToonyBricks game.
- Conducted a session to enlighten the benefits of Unity Unit Testing to my team.

# **VR** Welding

VR Weld is a product where Users can have a VR experience with different types of welding scenarios using a VR headset.

- Optimized the puddle getting generated in the current project by using low poly models, Unity's Mesh combine.
- Applied marching cubes algorithm
- Created custom color-changing shader from glowing yellow to red and then to original grey for puddles based on data of vertices sent to extra uv channels.

#### **Booster Ballz**

Booster Ballz is an endless runner where the ball needs to jump on marching colored tile along with some great powerups.

- Code Optimised for performance enhancement
- Applied camera occlusion culling for reducing unnecessary rendering.
- Baked Lightmaps to enhance the look and feel.

# ML Robot Arm

This is a simulation project where a human sitting in a wheelchair is getting food and water with the help of a Robot arm using Unity's MLAgent

- Created a Proper testable environment containing human, robotic arm, reward functions, and episode end cases.
- Provided flow diagrams of code workflow.
- Trained the environment by PPO and SAC algorithm.
- · Checked the TensorFlow graphs for a maximum rewarding agent and alter the YAML parameters for algorithms to yield maximum results.
- Compared the result by generating python graphs.

### TransfrVR

TRANSFR VR's core technology is a dialogue system between the trainee and a virtual coach. This unique VR apprenticeship model lets trainees move at their own pace and provides strategic, specific feedback to help them learn from their mistakes and master the skills they need to successfully perform their job.

I have worked with them in a few of their simulations such as

- Single Conduit Install One
- · Overhead branch install Two

The whole simulation is developed for each of the 3 steps Automated tutorial, Hands-on Practice, and On your own.

- Created custom extensions to reduce redundant code.
- Created custom generic conditions which massively reduce dependable code.
- · Worked with nested prefabs to manage simultaneous workflow between other team members.
- helped with creative decisions to improve the simulation.